Mmm.. What happened? What are you thinking about?
I ..
I wish to continue my practice after marriage
Cooking?
In that case you must start immediately
because our marriage is going to be soon.
It’s not that.
a clinic of my own
It’s my dream!
Practice?
But..
we are going to the States after our marriage
Yes..but..
Sister , they are asking for both of you downstairs.
We’ll be right there.
can’t we try at any hospitals over there?
Sandhya..
am earning enough for both of us to live comfortably..
and besides,
when I travel for my business purposes.
there should be someone at home
But Rahul..
my studies…
Moreover ..
if they hear your rant about wanting to work,
my mother and my relatives would laugh at me.
Sister, would you help me catch the balloon?
Hey , as I told you
Yea, I’ve liked her
Now..
rest will proceed according to my mom’s wishes.
Listen, shall I call you later?
I was speaking to Sandhya right now.
Both of you are wanted downstairs.
Aunty..
here’s  a joke!
Seems like Sandhya wants to start a clinic in America after the wedding
What is so funny, child?
Sandhya says she wants to work after marriage.
There is really no need.
You don’t have to work for a living.
You just have to go there and enjoy your life, my child.
But aunty ..
..MBBS is hard earned..
You don’t have to work hard now
earns enough for both of you ..
and your future generations.
Besides,
if our relatives come to know that our daughter-in-law is working
they would laugh at us.
Listen Mr. Madhu..
There have been one-after-the other marriage proposals for him.
Everyone is just waiting to snatch him away.
but he ,
wasn’t interested in any of them ,
until he saw Sandhya’s photograph.
Does she cook?
Yes,
she cooks well.
Great!
He just loves pineapple pullissery (curry).
But he doesn’t manage to get it made there in America.
And moreover,
its not like in here
servant there charges atleast 40000 rupees.
From now on,
it’s your responsibility to take care of him.
Please have the sweets.
Yes we will.
How long has Rahul’s sister been married?
2 years.
They are in Germany these days
They’ll reach here in time for the wedding .
Her wedding was a grand ceremony.
The celebrations went on for 5 days.
As you know, the marriage is borne by bride’s family.
So, we didn’t compromise on anything.
We gifted them 75 lakhs in money and a Benz car.
But, we won’t be asking you any dowry for his wedding.
We are sure you’ll do the needful.
Isn’t it?
Yes
Nobody should feel that he received any less than what was given to his sister.
Excuse me, I’ll be right back.
Manu,
will you please drop me.
My car away for servicing.
Oh yes,
I myself am about to leave. Let’s go
Hey Manu!
Did you hear..
that when Phase three opens,
there would be more than 5000 new job openings?
I’ve been trying to untangle this knot,
and along comes new one!
You look quite dull , Manu!
I’m tired of this job.
These deadlines and over -times!
There is practically no life here,
other than making some money.
Computers are eating away all the good days of my life.
You feel so because you are idle.
Weren’t you passionate about photography?
I haven’t seen your camera since long.
How can I click the camera,
when I don’t find time from clicking the mouse!
Earlier I was active in community services;
I used to teach kids.
Though it never earned me much money ,
it gave me a lot of happiness.
You can’t anticipate only happiness in life.
That’s true.
Else I would have left this job long back.
Everyone here is selfish.
They lack any sincerity or commitment towards others.
What meaning does it all have?
There is politics even in our office.
And, when we step out,
they discriminate based on caste, religion and such nonsense.
What’s wrong is this attitude.
Are you emulating  Dileep’s role in Kadhavaseshan ?
This is not something we can change.
This will change only if we make an effort!
This attitude has to change!
Hey, Manu, lookout!
Manu… Manu, stop!
Why can’t you turn on the indicator before taking a turn?!
It’s not enough to just know how to drive,
you need some civic sense too!
Did I hit your car!
You were over speeding and now you are blaming me?
what happened?
He was over speeding and blaming me.
Me!?
Manu!
Manu! please come lets go!
Oh!
you have a chick in the car!
No wonder,
you didn’t see the auto and the people around
Manu No! Stop! Please!
Hey! Stop your show off here!
Girl, ask him to leave!
Take your car and leave!
They didn’t start the fight!
Something? Didn’t you hear what they said!?
This isn’t just frustration.
And if, god forbid,  they are turn out to be techies,
That’s why I said that the mentality of the society here has to change to make this place any better!
The world deserves to hear your reaction.
People need to understand
into the societies’ pulse.
and analyse it if it makes sense to you.
on TV all one hears about are news about ‘abuses’.
Who wouldn’t rape these women
These dresses don’t even cover them properly.
Don’t blame it on women’s dress.
If our maid comes here wearing a short skirt?
A 12 year old girl was raped in our locality.
Speak softly. He can hear us!
Aunty is Gautham here?
Gautham, your friends are here!
I wish to fly like a balloon
I will fly, because I am superman!
Girls die because of it.
Girls die?
girls are raped because they wear short dresses.
?Is my dress short?
You mean ‘peedanam’ ( abuse)?
I have heard that on TV.
Grandma, what is the meaning ‘peedanam’ ( abuse)?
I have told you several times
Mom said girls are raped when they turn 12.
No don’t. They might scold you.
I heard my dad asking my mom to talk softly
She would have told me if something happened.
What will we do if someone comes to rape Malu ?
Come, let’s go and play.
Why, are you scared to lose to the boys?
No! Boys are smart! You can’t beat us if 3 of us join together!
Boys are smart. We will protect you.
Now that I’m going to the States only to take care of Rahul,
But you don’t worry aunty,
I will take very good care of your son.
I’ll prepare pineapple pulissery (curry) for him.
But, I don’t want  to be paid 40000 rupees,
I should have atleast told her this much.
I don’t wish to join those who proclaim that
Kerala is losing its power to react,
Instead, I feel our responses are limited
I don’t want to join the majority who hide and react.
Most of the times the society tries to hold us down,
never letting us soar high.
which wants to free itself into the air.
It is high time we break free
We shouldn’t tie the future generation
We should break all these ties which hold us back.