the greatest treasure by Ahmet Garg one
day Peter found a treasure map hooray
I'm going to find this treasure and have
some adventure he exclaimed
[Music]
Peter set off he walked a long way and
finally reached a forest there he met
lion you are strong and courageous said
Peter - lion will you come with me on a
treasure hunt
lion agreed and joined Peter the forest
was dense and dark
Peter was afraid but with lion by his
side he made it through when the two
finally reached the mountain they met
eagle you have excellent vision and can
alert us to dangers said Peter to Eagle
will you come with us we're looking for
a treasure Eagle agreed and joined Peter
and lion the mountains were tall and
craggy lion slipped but Peter was Swift
enough to give him a hand and pull him
up
[Music]
egle with his sharp vision watched every
step they took soon they reached the
valley below where they met sheep will
you join us in our search for a treasure
Peter asked cheap and keep us warm when
it's cold
[Music]
sheep agreed and joined Peter lion and
eagle a cold wind swept across the
endless meadow they all huddled against
sheep who kept them warm and cozy the
four finally reached the desert where
they met camel you are called the ship
of the desert said Peter to camel will
you help us get across and join the
treasure hunt - camel agreed Peter
lion and sheep mounted the camel and set
off happily across the vast desert with
Eagle enjoying the spectacle from above
[Music]
camel began galloping and everybody
cheered with excitement crossing the
desert on camel's back was thrilling the
five finally reached the ocean where
they met turtle can you help us cross
the ocean Peter asked turtle we're on a
treasure hunt
turtle agreed and joined Peter lion
Eagle sheep and camel
the rough waves almost drowned the party
but turtle skillfully transported them
across they met owl on the other side
owl spoke from his ancient wisdom
congratulations you have found the
treasure where is it they all exclaimed
in surprise together you have passed the
forest climbed the mountains dared the
valley braved the desert and cross the
ocean you would never have done it
without one another they all looked at
each other and realized that al was
right they had found friendship indeed
they had found the greatest treasure
ever
[Music]