Hey!
I know we haven't seen each other
And we haven't talked to each other in  while
But I want to you know
That I've been doing a lot of thinking lately..
...and...
I want to you know that
I miss you.
Not
I regret what happened
or
I want to see you again
Just...
I miss you.
It's so strange to think that someone I knew so well
Is now a total stranger to me
That sometimes I go entire days without thinking about you
Most of the time, I let myself forget
because it's easier
But then I find something
a photo
a gift
the stupid love letters we used to give eachother
and the full weight of  what's been lost  crashes down on me
part of me wants to see you again
to hold you again
to kiss you again
but all those feelings become empty thoughts
when I look back now
remember being love isn't always what it seems
it's just so easy to forget
but this isn't regret
we have a reasons for ending it
and they are as valid as ever
but back at the start
we didn't need any reasons to fall in love
we just did
the reasons came at the end
and everything since than has been about reasons
and that's good
means that one day I'll find someone who I won't have to say goodbye to
but...
a part of me just misses loving someone
and having them love you back
that's all
I guess what I'm saying is
I hope things are good with you
I hope everything it's great
I hope you found a love
that's all the things ours couldn't be
but...
just a small part of me hopes that you still remember what it was like
before all the reasons
and that
you miss me
too.